The Last Kingdom: Seven Kings Must Die is a action,
adventure, war film directed by Edward Bazalgette.
In the wake of King Edward's death, Uhtred of Bebbanburg and his comrades adventure
across a fractured kingdom in the hopes of uniting England at last.
Uhtred, played by Alexander Dreymon.
Aethelstan, played by Harry Gilby.
Finan, played by Mark Rowley.
Sihtric, played by Arnas Fedaravičius.
Pyrlig, played by Cavan Clerkin.
Aldhelm, played by James Northcote.
The Last Kingdom: Seven Kings Must Die is a 2023 British historical drama film directed by Edward Bazalgette,
written by Martha Hillier and based on The Saxon Stories series of novels by Bernard Cornwell.
It is the sequel and conclusion to the television series The Last Kingdom.
The series regulars Alexander Dreymon, Harry Gilby, Mark Rowley, Arnas Fedaravicius, Cavan Clerkin, James Northcote,
Ross Anderson, Ilona Chevakova, Rod Hallett, Ewan Horrocks and Steffan Rhodri reprise their roles.
It was released on 14 April 2023 on Netflix.
The film explores themes of fight, kingdom, heir to the
throne, battle for power, vikings (norsemen).